You are living in blessings daily
[music]
that someone else is praying for.
Convincing yourself [music] that you're
messing up. The person drowning in work
dreams of more free time. The person
with more free time dreams of having a
purpose. We are literally [music]
spending our lives standing in blessings
other people dream of. Other people are
praying for. Other people wish for every
day. Convincing ourselves that we are
missing out on something.
>> And that, I think, is the problem.
Happiness is not found in getting the
next thing.
>> It's found in finally seeing what you've
already got right in front of you.
>> Right? A roof, running water, food,
people that love you, a body that still
gets up in the morning and moves. Truth
is, most of us are not lacking
blessings.
Most of us are lacking perspective.
[music]
So, before you spend the rest of your
day wishing your life was different, I
want you to take inventory [music] of
the things that you would be absolutely
devastated
if you lost tomorrow. If you woke up
tomorrow and they were just gone. And
then I want you to choose to be
grateful
for those things.
Worry about that.
Happy Monday.